authenteak.com 2016-10-14

# AuthenTEAK is secure and never shares customer info | Privacy Policy

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://info.yahoo.com/privacy/us/yahoo/details.html) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

Privacy Statement for AuthenTEAK LLC

We respect your privacy, and we want you to feel comfortable using our website. Therefore, we are providing you with this privacy policy so you can better understand what information we collect from you, what we do with your information, and who, other than AuthenTEAK L.L.C. (“We,” “Us” or “Our”) may also receive your information.

This privacy policy is consistent with the Safe Harbor privacy provisions for transfers of personal information from the European Economic Area to the United States.

As you read through this privacy policy, please remember that you do not need to provide any information that identifies you in order to visit our website. In general, you can use many of the features of our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information whatsoever.

What Information Do We Collect From You?  
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (such as their name, email and postal address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level) (collectively, “Customer Information”).  
If you purchase products through our website, or if you want more information about our company, you will be required to complete an order form. The order form requires you to provide us with your Customer Information, as well as your credit card number (for purchases only).

What Do We Do With Your Customer Information?  
Our licensed distributors and we hold all Customer Information in the strictest of confidence. The information we collect is used solely for billing and shipping purposes, to provide you with information about our company, or for you to receive further product information.  
You may opt-out of receiving future mailings using the “Choice / Opt-out Procedures” described below.   
We may disclose your Customer Information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).

On occasion, we may hire third parties to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include removing repetitive information from our database, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These third parties have access to your Customer Information to the extent necessary to permit them to do their jobs, however, they may not use it for other purposes.

As AuthenTEAK LLC and its subsidiaries continue to grow and develop, we might sell our assets to third parties as part of a merger or sale of our business. In such transactions, Customer Information may be one of the transferred business assets.

In addition, we may use the information we obtain from our customers in the aggregate to determine our customers’ demographics and preferences. By doing so, we are able to deliver targeted services on our website which you may find to be helpful and informative.

Other than as stated in this Privacy Policy, we will not release your Customer Information to unknown or unaffiliated third parties, and we will not cross-reference your Customer Information with that of any other customer or entity.

How Do I Revise My Customer Information?  
In order that you receive the full benefit of our products and services, you should make sure that we have the most up-to-date information about you. Please remember that we will not remind you to update your information, nor will we necessarily verify that your information is correct, and so it is your responsibility to make sure that we have your correct information on file.

If you want to find out about or change your account information, simply send an email to [info@authenteak.com](mailto:info@authenteak.com), or call us at 404-525-1995. Please be sure to have your account information at hand when calling us, as we will need that information to locate your account.

Choice / Opt-Out Procedures  
If you do not want to receive future mailings and/or promotional information from us, you may opt out of receiving such information by sending an email to the following address: [info@authenteak.com](mailto:info@authenteak.com).

Alternatively, you can opt out by calling us at 404-525-1995. Please be sure to have your account information at hand when you call.

Internet Privacy  
In order to provide better service, we will occasionally use a "cookie." A cookie is a small amount of data which our website stores on your computer, and which we can later retrieve. The cookie cannot be read by a site other than ours. We use cookies for a number of administrative purposes; for example, to store your preferences for certain kinds of information or to store a password so that you do not have to input it every time you visit our site. No cookie will contain information that will allow anyone to contact you via telephone, e-mail, or any other means. You can monitor our use of cookies on your computer by setting your Web browser to inform you when cookies are set, or you can prevent the cookies from being set entirely. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Please understand that if you disable the use of cookies on your computer, you may be unable to access certain portions or services of our website.

Security  
We work to protect the security of your credit card information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. Of course, even though we use security software on our website, it is still important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your credit card and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. 

Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)  
Our website is directed to the general public. We do not knowingly sell products or services for use by children. If you are under 18, you may use our website only with involvement and supervision of a parent or guardian. We reserve the right to cancel, without prior notice to you, any purchases that we know, or have reason to believe, were made by persons under the age of 18. 

Changes to Our Privacy Policy  
As our customers’ needs change, we may find it necessary to amend or revise this Privacy Policy. Any such revisions or additions will be posted on this page. Please re-visit this page from time to time to make sure that you are aware of any additions or revisions to this policy. If you have any concern about privacy at our website, please send us a thorough description to [info@authenteak.com](mailto:info@authenteak.com) and we will try to resolve it. 

Electronic Notification  
When you purchase any products or services through our website, you consent to receive any privacy or other notices, agreements, disclosures, reports, documents, communications, or other records (collectively, “Notices”), whether or not the Notices are related to the products or services you purchased, from us electronically. You consent to receive Notices electronically in either or both of the following ways: 

A. We may post the Notice on our website; or  
B. We may transmit the Notice to you by email. 

If you do not wish to receive Notices from us electronically, you should not purchase any goods or services from us through our website.

All Notices provided to you electronically will be deemed to be "in writing." You acknowledge and agree that your consent to receive Notices electronically is being provided in connection with a transaction affecting interstate commerce that is subject to the federal Electronic Signatures in Global and National Commerce Act, and that we both intend that the Act apply to the fullest extent possible to validate our ability to conduct business with you by electronic means. 

In order to receive Notices electronically from us, you must have:

A. An Internet browser, such as Internet Explorer 4.0 or greater or Netscape Navigator 4.0 or greater;  
B. An email account and email software;  
C. A personal computer, operating system and telecommunications connections to the Internet capable of supporting the foregoing;  
D. Sufficient electronic storage capacity on your computer’s hard drive or other data storage unit; and  
E. A printer that is capable of printing from your browser and email software.

Your Options  
Should you choose not to accept the terms outlined in this privacy policy, or any modified or revised version hereof, you may withdraw as a current customer from our website. To withdraw, you must contact us at the email addresses listed above, and provide us with your Customer Information. If you withdraw as a current customer of our website, we may retain your Customer Information we have collected up to the date of your withdrawal, however, we will not disclose your Customer Information from that point forward, except as permitted by law.

SPECIAL PROVISIONS FOR INFORMATION RECEIVED BY US FROM OUR CUSTOMERS IN THE EUROPEAN UNION:

SAFE HARBOR PRIVACY PROVISIONS  
We respect individual privacy and value the confidence that our European friends and customers place in us. The following Safe Harbor Privacy Policies set forth the privacy principles that we follow with respect to personal information transferred from the European Economic Area (EEA) (which includes the fifteen member states of the European Union (EU) plus Iceland, Liechtenstein and Norway) to the United States.

**SAFE HARBOR**  
The United States Department of Commerce and the European Commission have agreed on a set of data protection principles and frequently asked questions (the "Safe Harbor Principles") to enable U.S. companies to satisfy the requirement under EU law that protection be given to personal information transferred from the EU to the United States. The EEA also has recognized the U.S. Safe Harbor as providing adequate data protection (OJ L 45, 15.2.2001, p.47). Consistent with its commitment to protect personal privacy, AuthenTEAK LLC adheres to the Safe Harbor Principles. 

**SCOPE**  
This Safe Harbor Privacy Policy (“Safe Harbor Policy”) applies to all personal information received by us in the United States from the European Economic Area, regardless of the format by which we receive such information.

**DEFINITIONS**  
For purposes of this Safe Harbor Policy, the following definitions shall apply: 

"Agent" means any third party that collects or uses personal information under the instructions of, and solely for, us or to which we disclose personal information for use on our behalf. 

“AuthenTEAK LLC,” “We,” "Us," or “Our” means AuthenTEAK LLC, and its successors, subsidiaries, divisions and groups in the United States.

"Personal information" means any information or set of information that identifies or is used by or on behalf of us to identify an individual. Personal information does not include information that is encoded or anonymized, or publicly available information that has not been combined with non-public personal information. 

"Sensitive personal information" means personal information that reveals race, ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, or that concerns health or sex life. In addition, we will treat as sensitive personal information any information received from a third party where that third party treats and identifies the information as sensitive. 

**PRIVACY PRINCIPLES  
** The following policies are based on the Safe Harbor Principles. 

**NOTICE** **:** Where we collect personal information directly from individuals in the EEA, we will inform those individuals about the purposes for which we collect and use their personal information, the types of non-agent third parties to which we may disclose that information, and the choices and means, if any, we offer individuals for limiting the use and disclosure of their personal information. Notice will be provided in clear and conspicuous language at the time that such individuals are first asked to provide personal information to us, or as soon as practicable thereafter, and in any event before we use or disclose the information for a purpose other than that for which it was originally collected. 

**CHOICE** **:** We will offer individuals the opportunity to choose (opt-out) whether their personal information is (a) to be disclosed to a non-agent third party, or (b) to be used for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. 

For sensitive personal information, we will give individuals the opportunity to affirmatively and explicitly (opt-in) consent to the disclosure of the information to a non-agent third party or the use of the information for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. 

We will provide individuals with reasonable options to exercise their choices, including but not limited to those options provided to our Non-EEA customers. 

**DATA INTEGRITY** **:** We will use personal information only in ways that are compatible with the purposes for which it was collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that personal information is relevant to its intended use, accurate, complete, and current. 

**TRANSFERS TO AGENTS** **:** We will obtain assurances from our agents that they will safeguard personal information consistently with the policies listed in this Safe Harbor Policy. Examples of appropriate assurances that may be provided by agents include: a contract obligating the agent to provide at least the same level of protection as is required by the relevant Safe Harbor Principles, being subject to EU Directive 95/46/EC (the EU Data Protection Directive), Safe Harbor certification by the agent, or being subject to another European Commission adequacy finding (e.g., companies located in Hungary and Switzerland). Where we have knowledge that an agent is using or disclosing personal information in a manner contrary to this Policy, we will take reasonable steps to prevent or stop the use or disclosure. 

**ACCESS AND CORRECTION** **:** Upon request, we will grant individuals reasonable access to personal information that we hold about them. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to permit individuals to correct, amend, or delete information that is demonstrated to be inaccurate or incomplete. 

**SECURITY** **:** We will take reasonable precautions to protect personal information in our possession from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. 

**ENFORCEMENT** **:** We will, at our discretion, conduct compliance audits of our relevant privacy practices to verify our adherence to this Policy. Any employee that we determine is in violation of our privacy policies will be subject to disciplinary action up to and including termination of employment. Further, we will comply with private sector developed privacy programs that incorporate the Safe Harbor Principles into their rules, including but not limited to monitoring by BBBOnline.com, as well as monitoring by the Federal Trade Commission of the United States government.

**DISPUTE RESOLUTION** **:** Any questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of personal information should be directed to us at the address given below. We will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of personal information in accordance with the principles described herein. 

**LIMITATION ON APPLICATION OF PRINCIPLES**  
Adherence by us to these Safe Harbor Principles may be limited (a) to the extent required to respond to a legal or ethical obligation; and (b) to the extent expressly permitted by an applicable law, rule or regulation. Adherence may be further limited to the extent that disclosure of personal information is necessary to (1) protect and defend our rights and property; (2) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website; or (3) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public.

**CONTACT INFORMATION FOR SAFE HARBOR CONCERNS**  
Questions or comments regarding this Safe Harbor Policy should be submitted to us by mail or e-mail as follows: 

AuthenTEAK LLC  
1094 Huff Road  
Atlanta, GA 30318 USA

**CHANGES TO THIS SAFE HARBOR PRIVACY POLICY**  
This Policy may be amended from time to time, consistent with the requirements of the Safe Harbor Principles. A notice will be posted on our website for sixty (60) days whenever this Safe Harbor Privacy Policy is changed in a material way. 

EFFECTIVE DATE: January 1, 2016.
